const questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "A college degree alone ensures career growth.",
    answer: "True",
    options: ["False", "True"]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How can one effectively learn a new skill?",
    answer: "Choose, learn deeply, and practice",
    options: [
      "Choose, learn deeply, and practice",
      "Join online forums and discussions",
      "Read books and watch videos",
      "Attend seminars and workshops"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "A successful career requires removing distractions and maintaining ____ and dedication.",
    answer: "discipline",
    options: [
      "motivation",
      "curiosity",
      "discipline",
      "interest"]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b> <i>: Harry has completed a course in data analysis and is now looking for his first job. He wants to ensure that the job offers opportunities for growth and international exposure.</i><br><b>Identify the incorrect job feature for growth.</b>`,
    answer: "Limited learning opportunities",
    options: [
      "Work-life balance",
      "Job security",
      "Promotions",
      "Limited learning opportunities"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b> <i>Harry is planning to learn a new skill to enhance his career prospects. He is evaluating different skills and resources to ensure he chooses the right one for his IT career.</i><br><b>Which one of the following is a correct step for skill development?</b>`,
    answer: "Practice by building real projects",
    options: [
      "Practice by building real projects",
      "Focus on multiple skills at once",
      "Avoid online learning platforms",
      "Skip skill evaluation and start immediately"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Is discipline crucial for a successful career?",
    answer: "Yes",
    options: ["No", "Yes"]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is essential for career growth in IT?",
    answer: "Skill development and real project practice",
    options: [
      "Networking and social media presence",
      "Only a college degree",
      "Attending industry conferences",
      "Skill development and real project practice"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "To launch your website, first create an account on A career growth oriented job offers job security, promotions, and ____ opportunities.",
    answer: "international",
    options: ["temporary", "international", "limited", "local"]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b> <i>Harry is considering a career in IT. He is unsure which skills to focus on to ensure job security and growth. He has access to various online learning platforms and is seeking guidance on the best approach to build his skills.</i><br><b>Identify the incorrect step for career growth.</b>`,
    answer: "Focus on multiple skills at once",
    options: [
      "Get your first job",
      "Remove distractions and discouragement",
      "Learn one right skill",
      "Focus on multiple skills at once"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b> <i>Harry is overwhelmed by the number of skills he can learn. He wants to focus on skills that will provide job security and growth in the IT industry.</i><br><b>Which one of the following is a correct skill to focus on for IT growth?</b>`,
    answer:"Data analysis",
    options: [
      "Data analysis",
      "Content creation",
      "2D animation",
      "Video editing"
    ]
  }
];
